(Q11（table横纵表格填空）) ⭐ be delighted to do sth —— 很高兴做某事｜be interested in... —— 对……感兴趣｜plants and creatures —— 植物和生物
⭐ be surprised at... —— 对……感到惊讶｜a variety of... —— 各种各样的……
⭐ start by doing sth —— 以做某事开始｜open spaces —— 开放区域；空地｜nearby —— 附近的
⭐ pleasant place —— 宜人的地方
⭐ public land —— 公共土地｜for hundreds of years —— 数百年来｜flow into the sea —— 流入大海｜have its source in... —— 发源于……
⭐ information board —— 信息牌｜by the way —— 顺便说一下｜be accessible —— 可进入的；开放使用的
(Q12) ⭐ be noted for... —— 因……而闻名｜a great range of... —— 大量不同种类的……
⭐ commercially —— 商业性地｜basket-making —— 编篮｜ancient craft —— 古老工艺｜be reintroduced —— 被重新引入
⭐ be open to the public —— 对公众开放｜keep away —— 避开；远离
(Q13) ⭐ a short walk —— 很短的步行距离｜across the bridge —— 过桥
⭐ replica of... —— ……的复制品｜over two thousand years ago —— 两千多年前
⭐ activities are arranged —— 活动被安排｜bread-making —— 制作面包｜face-painting —— 脸部彩绘
⭐ during daylight hours —— 白天时间｜bear something in mind —— 记住某事
(Q14（单选）) ⭐ programme of activities —— 活动计划｜throughout the year —— 全年｜give you a sample —— 给你一个例子
⭐ herbs —— 草药｜over the centuries —— 几个世纪以来
⭐ start with... —— 从……开始｜tour of... —— ……参观｜technique of doing sth —— 做某事的技术｜colour dyes —— 染料
⭐ illustrated talk —— 图文讲座｜use in... —— 在……中的用途
(Q15) ⭐ join experts —— 加入专家团队｜a variety of... —— 各种各样的……｜appear in the evening —— 晚上出现
⭐ keep to a number —— 限制在某个数量｜a small number of... —— 少量……｜a few days ahead —— 提前几天｜park ranger —— 公园管理员
⭐ a small charge —— 小额费用｜turn up —— 到达；出现
(Q16) ⭐ be keen to do sth —— 热衷于做某事｜look after —— 照顾｜working party —— 工作小组
⭐ a choice of... —— ……的选择｜all sorts of... —— 各种各样的……｜plant hedges —— 种植树篱｜pick up litter —— 捡垃圾｜feel like doing sth —— 想做某事
⭐ ranger 护林员; 公园管理员 ｜be hard at work —— 努力工作｜join in —— 参与
⭐ make sure —— 确保｜don't mind doing sth —— 不介意做某事｜get dirty/torn —— 变脏/破损
(Q17（地图题）) ⭐ wildlife area —— 野生动物区域｜be opened to the public —— 向公众开放
⭐ indicate —— 表明；显示｜main paths —— 主要道路
⭐ north west —— 西北｜bird hide —— 观鸟屋｜at the end of... —— 在……尽头
⭐ a quiet place for doing sth —— 做某事的安静场所
(Q18) ⭐ refreshments —— 饮料；点心｜fairly close to... —— 相当靠近……｜dog-walking area —— 遛狗区域｜lead off from... —— 从……延伸出去
(Q19) ⭐ sit and relax —— 坐下休息｜circular area —— 圆形区域｜be surrounded by... —— 被……包围
(Q20) ⭐ wooded area —— 林区｜western section —— 西部区域｜between two paths —— 两条路之间
⭐ that's enough from me —— 我就讲到这里